[
  {
    "question": "apple",
    "answer": "jabłko"
  },
  {
    "question": "car",
    "answer": "samochód"
  },
  {
    "question": "house",
    "answer": "dom"
  },
  {
    "question": "book",
    "answer": "książka"
  },
  {
    "question": "water",
    "answer": "woda"
  },
  {
    "question": "to see",
    "answer": "widzieć"
  },
  {
    "question": "to go",
    "answer": "iść, jechać"
  },
  {
    "question": "to have",
    "answer": "mieć"
  },
  {
    "question": "to want",
    "answer": "chcieć"
  },
  {
    "question": "good",
    "answer": "dobry"
  },
  {
    "question": "bad",
    "answer": "zły"
  },
  {
    "question": "big",
    "answer": "duży"
  },
  {
    "question": "small",
    "answer": "mały"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello",
    "answer": "Cześć / Dzień dobry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Goodbye",
    "answer": "Do widzenia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "Dziękuję"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Tak"
  },
  {
    "question": "No",
    "answer": "Nie"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your name?",
    "answer": "Jak masz na imię?"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are you?",
    "answer": "Jak się masz?"
  }
]